supercontrol.co.uk 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy | SuperControl

We are committed to ensuring the best standards of practice in all our activities. Visitors to our web site can be assured that the protection of privacy and confidentiality are given the highest priority. All personal information is collected, held and used in strict compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

 **Information Collected**  
We do not collect any personal information from visitors to our website other than information that is knowingly and voluntarily given. Anonymous information is collected, such as the number of visitors to the website in a given period, but it is purely statistical and cannot be used to identify an individual user. Cookies are not used to collect any other information from visitors to the website. Visitors interested in requesting more information can provide contact details via a fill-in form. Visitors cannot be contacted unless such information is given. Visitors are also invited to give additional company information but a decision not to do so does not affect any subsequent negotiations or discussions.

 **Use of Information**  
The information collected will be used to contact you with further details of our current activities or to send details of future initiatives or events. It may also be used for research purposes. You can inform us at any time if you no longer require such information to be sent.

If you provide your email address to us, you agree that we may send information to you by email in relation to our Services and in relation to any new services, initiatives or events. You will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from any such emails at any time.

Occasionally, we may share your details with certain carefully selected third parties for the purposes of contacting you to provide information on certain related services to our own services by email or by telephone. We always vet our partner organisations thoroughly and we will NEVER sell your details to any third party. You consent to us providing your details to our carefully selected third parties in this way. You will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from any such emails or telephone calls at any time.

 **Data Security**  
We take appropriate measures to safeguard the information we hold from unauthorised access or improper use. Our database is stored in a secure, password protected location. Only users authorised by us have access to this data.

 **Integrity of Data**  
We take all reasonable measures to ensure that the information we hold is accurate. In particular we use reliable collection methods and destroy or convert to an anonymous form, any out-of-date data. Individuals may request details of all personal information held by us so as to contest inaccurate or incomplete data, verify the information and have it corrected as appropriate.

 **Children**  
Our website is not targeted at children but in any event personal information will not knowingly be collected from children under fourteen years without parental consent.

 **Enforcement**  
Any queries relating to our collection or use of personal information should be addressed to [support@supercontrol.co.uk](mailto:support@supercontrol.co.uk).
